Sowmya Karanth Finance Analyst

Hyderabad, Telangana - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Sowmya-Karanth/ a76c9c40c02ed396

To leverage 1+ years experience in order management and build up the core financial techniques

ensure the better growth of the organisation by providing dedicated and on time delivery of the job.

Willing to relocate to: Bengaluru, Karnataka - hyderbad, Telangana - Chennai, Tamil Nadu

WORK EXPERIENCE

Finance Analyst

Oracle India Pvt ltd -

May 2015 to March 2017

- * Recruited as Finance analyst for NAMER (North Americas') region and worked for a year.
- * Achieved 'YAR (You Are Recognised) ' Award for the month of August 2015 and was given the title "Young and early achiever".
- * From June 2016 to September 2016 was trained and worked for EMEA (Middle Eastern) regions and was the mentor for new joiners and trainer for new managers.
- * From September 2016 due to regional expansion was trained for APAC (Asian & Pacific) regions and was given the title 'Global Resource' due to my constant & extensive support for the other two regions.
- * Performed two major projects 'LLC (License Learning Cycle) ' and 'Global Review tool' and was the lead and global reviewer in both.
- * Performed various extensive analysis to globalise the process like standardising the differences in the process flow and concepts between regions.

EDUCATION

MBA in Finance and sectorial specialisation

Avinashilingam Institute for Home Science & Higher Education for Women

2013 to 2015

French

https://www.indeed.com/r/Sowmya-Karanth/a76c9c40c02ed396?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=INhttps://www.indeed.com/r/Sowmya-Karanth/a76c9c40c02ed396?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN

S.B.K.V higher secondary school

2010

Avinashilingam Deemed University - Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu

SKILLS

EMPLOYEE RESOURCE GROUP (Less than 1 year), ENTERPRISE RESOURCE PLANNING (Less than 1 year), ERP (Less than 1 year), Microsoft office (Less than 1 year), MS OFFICE (Less than 1 year)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

/INTERESTS

* Computer skills - Microsoft office, ERP, Oracle SQL